Register of the Seymour Weiss papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Writings by Others, 1952-1992 (Box 21)
  - Hartley, Anthony, 1975 (Box-folder 21: 8)
  - Heisbourg, François, 1992 (Box-folder 21: 9)
  - Kissinger, Henry A., 1974-1992 (Box-folder 21: 10)
  - Klingberg, Frank L., 1952 (Box-folder 21: 11)
  - Kohler, Foy D., 1970-1975 (Box-folder 21: 12)
  - Kraemer, Fritz G. A., 1961 (Box-folder 21: 13)
  - Marshall, Charles Burton, 1970 (Box-folder 21: 14)
  - Nitze, Paul H., 1975 (Box-folder 21: 15)
  - Odom, William E., 1987 (Box-folder 21: 16)
  - Ra'anan, Uri, 1980 (Box-folder 21: 17)
  - Sloss, Leon, 1988 (Box-folder 21: 18)
  - Tarcov, Nathan, 1984 (Box-folder 21: 19)
  - Wohlstetter, Albert, 1973 (Box-folder 21: 20)
- Subject File, 1960-1994 (Boxes 21-26)
  - Arms control, 1987 (Box-folder 21: 21)
  - Ball, George W., 1987 (Box-folder 21: 22)
  - Baltic States, 1988 (Box-folder 21: 23)
  - BETA I and II war games, 1967 (Box-folder 22: 1)
  - Chronologies, 1963-1973 (Box-folder 22: 2)
  - Defense budget, 1964-1969
    - 1964 (Box-folder 22: 3)
    - 1965 (Box-folder 22: 4)
    - 1967 (Box-folder 22: 5)
    - 1969 (Box-folder 22: 6)
  - Defense industry, 1987 (Box-folder 22: 7)
  - Defense Nuclear Agency, 1980 (Box-folder 22: 8)
  - Defense Science Board, Task Force on Defense, Nuclear Agency Technology Base Program, 1981 (Box-folder 22: 9)
  - Détente, 1974-1975
    - 1974-1975 (Box-folder 23: 1)
    - 1975 (Box-folder 23: 2-3)
  - Intermediate-Range Nuclear Forces (INF) Treaty, 1987-1988
    - 1987-1988 (Box-folder 23: 4-6)
    - 1988 (Box-folder 23: 7-8)
  - Joint Strategic Target Planning Staff Scientific Advisory Board, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 24: 1)
  - Kemp, Jack, 1987 (Box-folder 24: 2-3)
  - Kennedy administration, 1974 (Box-folder 24: 4)
  - Kissinger, Henry, 1976 (Box-folder 24: 5)
  - National Archives, 1975-1993 (Box-folder 24: 6)
  - National security strategy, 1987 (Box-folder 24: 7)
  - National Security Archive, 1994 (Box-folder 24: 8)
  - North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO), 1980-1989 (Box-folder 24: 9-10)
  - Nuclear History Program, 1993 (Box-folder 24: 11)
  - Nuclear strategy, 1961-1992
    - 1961 (Box-folder 25: 1)
    - 1981 (Box-folder 25: 2)
    - 1982 (Box-folder 25: 3)
    - 1983 (Box-folder 25: 4)
    - 1984 (Box-folder 25: 5)
    - 1992 (Box-folder 25: 6)
  - Nuclear winter, 1985 (Box-folder 25: 7)
  - Reagan transition team, 1980 (Box-folder 25: 8)
  - Skybolt affair, 1963 (Box-folder 25: 9)
  - Soviet military, 1975 (Box-folder 25: 10)
  - Soviet military, 1975 (Box-folder 26: 1)
  - Soviet Union - Foreign relations, 1974 (Box-folder 26: 2)
  - Spiers, Ronald J., 1992 (Box-folder 26: 3)
  - Strategic Defense Initiative, 1990 (Box-folder 26: 4)
  - Team B, 1975-1988 (Box-folder 26: 5-6)
  - Technology transfer, 1980 (Box-folder 26: 7)
  - Troop withdrawals in Europe, 1966 (Box-folder 26: 8)
  - Test ban, 1976 (Box-folder 26: 9)
  - U.S./NATO relations, 1978-1981 (Box-folder 26: 10)
  - Vietnam, 1960 (Box-folder 26: 11)
- Photographs, 1965-1980 (Box 26)
  - 1 print depicting Seymour Weiss being awarded a State Department medal, 1968 (Box-folder 26: 12)
  - 1 print depicting Seymour Weiss arriving at a naval facility, 1972 (Box-folder 26: 13)
  - 1 print depicting Seymour Weiss on Face the Nation, 1974 (Box-folder 26: 14)
  - 12 prints depicting Seymour Weiss with various government officials, military officers, and other individuals, 1965-1980 (Box-folder 26: 15)
- Oversize Materials, 1958-1988 (Box 27)
  - Certificates, 1965-1988
    - Superior Honor Award, 1965 (Box-folder 27: 1)
    - Outstanding performance, 1969 (Box-folder 27: 2)
    - Outstanding performance, 1972 (Box-folder 27: 3)
    - Appointment, Director, Politico-Military Affairs, U.S. Department of State, 1973 (Box-folder 27: 4)
    - Official recognition and appreciation, 30 years of service, U.S. government, 1976 (Box-folder 27: 5)
    - Department of Defense Medal for Distinguished Public Service, 1977 (Box-folder 27: 6)
    - Recognition of exemplary service, presidential transition, 1981 (Box-folder 27: 7)
    - Meritorious public service citation, U.S. Department of the Navy, 1982 (Box-folder 27: 8)
    - Appointment, Member, Army Science Board, 1984 (Box-folder 27: 9)
    - Department of Defense Medal for Distinguished Public Service, 1987 (Box-folder 27: 10)
    - Appointment, Consultant, Army Science Board, 1988 (Box-folder 27: 11)
  - Medals, 1970
    - Superior Honor Award, U.S. Department of State, 1970 (Box-folder 27: 12)
    - Unidentified award, 1970 (Box-folder 27: 13)
  - Photographs, 1958-1986
    - 1 print depicting Seymour Weiss and others, 27th meeting of the Scientific Advisory Group, 1980 (Box-folder 27: 14)
    - 1 print depicting Seymour Weiss and Admiral William J. Crowe, 1985 (Box-folder 27: 15)
    - Inscribed portraits, 1958-1986
      - U. Alexis Johnson, 1958 (Box-folder 27: 16)
      - Elliot Richardson, 1970 (Box-folder 27: 17)
      - Earle G. Wheeler, 1970 (Box-folder 27: 18)
      - J. R. Halloway, 1971 (Box-folder 27: 19)
      - James D. Watkins, 1971 (Box-folder 27: 20)
      - Elmo Zumwalt, 1971 (Box-folder 27: 21)
      - Tom Hayward, 1972 (Box-folder 27: 22)
      - Carl Trost, 1986 (Box-folder 27: 23-24)
      - Unidentified, 1973 (Box-folder 27: 25)
  - Plaque in recognition of 31 years of service and dedication, U.S. government, 1977 (Box-folder 27: 26)
- Printed Matter, 1973-1994 (Box 28)
  - Pamphlet, Economics and Politics in Russia: Diagnosis, 1992 (Box-folder 28: 1)
  - Serial issues, 1973-1994
    - Bahamas, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 28: 2)
    - Cold War International History Project Bulletin, 1992-1994 (Box-folder 28: 3)
    - Department of State Newsletter, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 28: 4)